{
    "id": "339a049d6cbb44dc8e78780be20aab0d",
    "title": "Food Idioms Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "9eb54a5e31074129a778f28274000978",
            "title": "Food Idioms Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "The interview was as easy as ........................... and I am confident of getting the job.",
                    "description": "If something is as easy as pie, it is very easy.",
                    "answers": [
                        "pie",
                        "cake",
                        "sauce"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She seems to have a ................................. in every pie.",
                    "description": "To have a finger in every pie is to be involved in so many things. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "hand",
                        "finger",
                        "foot"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I thought the exam would be hard but it was a piece of ................................",
                    "description": "If something is a piece of cake, it is very easy to do.",
                    "answers": [
                        "pie",
                        "cake",
                        "cream"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Her dream of becoming a famous model remained a ................................ in the sky.",
                    "description": "A pie in the sky is an unrealistic dream.",
                    "answers": [
                        "star",
                        "pie",
                        "hole"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "It was a half-............................ plan, so I was not surprised when it failed.",
                    "description": "A half baked plan is something that is not thought through. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "boiled",
                        "cooked",
                        "baked"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "My landlady is as ................................. as a fruitcake. I can't get on with her anymore.",
                    "description": "As nutty as a fruitcake means very crazy.",
                    "answers": [
                        "sour",
                        "nutty",
                        "sweet"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "They were selling clothes for ................................ at the garage sale.",
                    "description": "For peanuts means cheap.",
                    "answers": [
                        "doughnuts",
                        "peanuts",
                        "nuts"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Although his project failed he was too proud to eat ...............................",
                    "description": "To eat crow is to admit that you made a mistake.",
                    "answers": [
                        "crow",
                        "chicken",
                        "hen"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "If you are a rich kid you may be used to getting everything handed to you on a ............................... platter.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "silver",
                        "gold",
                        "platinum"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "It is crucial to work hard. Keep in mind that there is no such thing as a free ..............................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "breakfast",
                        "lunch",
                        "dinner"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She would never have participated in that beauty contest if her parents hadn't ................................... her on.",
                    "description": "To egg someone on is to encourage them.",
                    "answers": [
                        "zeroed",
                        "egged",
                        "oiled"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I need a job to bring home the ………………………..",
                    "description": "To bring home the bacon is to earn money to live. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "chicken",
                        "mutton",
                        "bacon"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}